Babe, hi everybody
Hello go see oh Jamie
Dave
Hi guys
I think that is oh my gosh
I had a good night because
All right, my up my friends came over and
He's like,
he helped me clean.
Hi, Dave.
Launcher right there.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, hold on a second.
I need to find my phone thing.
Here it is.
Hi, guys.
Oh, here it is.
Hi
Sweetheart
Well the time is it's not early it's like 1145
What my friend just showed up different time schedules brother. Yeah
Wow
But uh, my friend came over and he was like hey
And uh, but it was quite it was a quiet stream. It was I like, you know, I I unmodded everybody
And then so I don't know necessarily quiet. I think that might have been a good fucking idea. Yeah
Yeah, well, it's like, you know, it was causing more conflict and it's like now everybody can just
Have fun in the chat. It's kind of funny. So like you were like, uh, like
I was literally just looking for open panels because nobody that I'm subscribed to was live
So I was looking for open panels that are alive all of a sudden you just popped up
So I said never find me you just popped up. I was alright. It's like five and it's going to buy in time
It's divine timing divine timing. Hey
That might have been a card brother that might have been a card
Oh my friend drink up my hit. Yeah, so uh, so but he was like, he's like, oh, yeah
She's like, but she wanted to help me clean clean up, you know, and that was really cool
She used to like be like a
Manager for like one of those maid services wherever she's but she's like, I love doing such and she was just uh, oh my god
She's like, you know, she's like clean my whole kitchen floor so beautiful and stuff. Oh my god
So I'm really you know
That we do have big people that looks like I got one question or if you don't mind me answering it
I don't want to count you on nothing, but I do have one question
Hmm
So maybe use magic in port of card and maybe I asked God and I was like I was really looking for an open panel
I thought that was really gonna help me
And I asked for that and then all of a sudden you popped up live
It's not any different than like maybe if I like pulled up a car and I was like, oh, you know
I thought I'm gonna do a live this night. I really want it and then like
You know it's only too deeply into it. It's just like, you know, I think it's like I just came across me the right place
You can't you have to though you believe in some shit. You better you better kind of dissect it, you know like
Well, cuz I got one. I'm not gonna bring it up, but I got one. Do you want to do it?
Do you want me to pull your car now? Do you want me to pull you one car tonight?
Yeah, it's my animal card. No, it's the Wonderland deck. It's a Disney's also wonderland
I want the animal card brother. Yeah, okay. I'll pull you up. I'll pull you in after I have the animal card
I haven't here, but I'll pull you one up. I'll pull you on from here first, okay?
Okay, give a number
I'm pulling it from this this deck about the house of wonderland first only one card. All right. Okay. Do you want two cards?
Oh, see we can do two cards. Okay. Okay. Yeah, why don't you whatever you you're the okay
I'll play you cuz you get more we get some good information from two. Okay, so
They pulled your cards. Okay
Okay, so you got okay, so you got okay the emperors okay, so you have the emperors and you have
this is the
Four of the four flowers you get the four flower which is the four of ones
And you have the emperors, okay, so
I don't know. I don't know. Do you have a girlfriend or something because the Empress is all the queens in the deck and so I don't I don't
I wish that would be emperor, but
Well the emperor, okay, so there's like four queens in the deck and they're you know, they're all the elements
There's a earth, air, fire, water
And that's you know
And air is like communication, earth is like, you know, the material world, you know, the ones are fire, and fire is like passion, and then the water represents emotion.
So this represents passion, and it's okay, so it's a four, okay.
Okay, and a question.
I agree with that one.
Well, so let me see where flowers does maybe too passionate sometimes before flowers is an exciting
celebratory
card suggesting you'll
You'll have
Do you just go? No, no, no
You just put me in a car and you don't know what the fuck it said. You just go with it
No, no, I know what it means. I know it's a four. I know it's a four ones
I mean, but I'm assuming this is because it's written well says four
Four flowers is an exciting celebrate story card suggesting that you'll have a cause to throw a
Fun tea party of your own very soon the card could be a family
Go ahead brother. Go ahead. Sorry. Sorry. I said it could be a family family reunion housewarming party of
Birthday or celebration for another
milestone in your life
Enjoy. Can I ask you a question about tarot with friends in love? Yes
Was that tarot reading correct or am I?
This is one right here. This is a tarot reading. Yes. Yeah
So it's like is there a death garden now?
Yes, there's a death card this way. I don't know if it's called desi might have so what would happen if you bought a death card for me
No, but that's
You know that boy, okay, by the way. Oh, yeah, I know how to fix it. I'm trying to fix it
All right, we will all we will all pass away, you know, it's like it's so likely, you know, and so
But so and you're gonna predict that shit
Well, so that you know at some time in everybody's life that the depth they're gonna be the death card, right?
It's like that's just life, right?
And in depth the death is also like an ending
But it can be an ending for something else because there's just there's things like there's lives and then there's projects
There's ideas
100% agree with you
What I'm saying though is like I asked you for a card reading you pulled the death card
That's just probably gonna happen soon. So I should be prepared for death
No, because it could mean death of like something else other than a physical body
It doesn't necessarily mean me a physical death. I found my court. Hold on
He gave me and I can and I also it also means death
But it also means rebirth because it's like you know death, you know when something dies something else is born
So we don't really
Like a make a different form well the energy is never created to destroy
physics, but it could be reincarnation. Yeah, because it's like
I believe no matter what when you pull that death card. I am gonna die correct. Well, I mean
Doesn't necessarily mean any kind of physical death or anybody's
You know say one thing and then I'll I'll let you go because I don't want to debate you but
It fucks with free will right?
but no
Yeah, what's up, ghost? Yo thing that is you pull a car and it says oh
I'm gonna die that you're fucking with free will even god
You're gonna die though everyone boy
Hold on. Do you want to debate it? I'm dumb
Jacob
Are you gonna have it or hell you want to know what?
God he judges your heart you can even be like
You're gonna do a reading that's all I'm saying
All right, give me one minute porch
Well, you guys give up free will though like if it was predicted. No, it's not nothing to do
Well, listen, I actually just put a card in
I want to know am I going to have an arrow
Can you tell this guy to just stop talking during our reading
come on. Yeah. Well, don't ask him for a reading. He literally just seconds not going to determine that. So, if you ask him for a reading, if I'm going to heaven or hell, what you don't even believe in. I'm not talking about you. As far as I know, the cards can't tell you that. Well, it doesn't matter. It doesn't matter, man. I'm just talking to you.
Go go fucking screw your child and the fucking dog in your house. Oh, I'm talking to me like that
I
Was talking but you're not gonna talk to me like that believe that
See what happens
I would have a good energy, so let's see if I can
You know that's an epic question, you know it's a kind of a yes or no question. Okay, so okay, so we have we have this done
Okay, so you have the Sun car, okay?
Where you
Yeah, we're not starting with white women. That's not good. No, okay
You know so it's the time card so the Sun is like another celestial body. It's also the most
So I would say that has to do with heaven. Okay. What's I can get okay? Yeah, so I would say the answer for you
I'll answer another one, but I'll bring back at the stop for a second
I'm doing show man. There's people yelling in the background man. I
Didn't hear anything. I don't know what you're talking about
No, you not you idiot the guy who's showing us the cards
Yeah, it was a phone call. It was a ringtone and then you fucking answered the phone. That's why you left I
Never left you idiot
We're not talking about you. We're talking you just are you dumb I
Think you are and you are ghost. How am I dumb? Okay? How am I dumb because you're a nigger?
You beat bitches and there you go
There you go. That's your argument. Good argument brother. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, shut up
I don't know. Actually, I don't want you should probably leave though. You just said the n-word
Okay, but also
I want a dumbass. I don't have one white friend. Every friend that have is black and brown. Don't care
Okay, yeah
This is I'm the reader. I'm reading your card right now. I think I'm reading your card. I'm a states are a porch
I've read before to start right. Yes. Who has no day we're going to have it or not porch
You was reading that for all from me site. Oh
Stay time. Well, you know, let's say sorry. Okay
The you said the Sun card and it had the yeah, okay, yeah, okay the Sun card
But the car before it's also has this that's a 10 of 10 of flowers, which is like
It means it means like a lot of hard work it means even like you know, you know taking on others others
burdens and stuff like that and this is like but it looks like I like
But then it looks like you know, you guys about heaven and it's like and then it looks like you know, just
What she's being she's being it means like just you can pretend that's you even though it's a you know, a white white
Um, it's he's being served and she's in like a very happy place. It's like it is. It looks like I have been they play
So it looks like after a lot of hard work girl receive some much easier relaxation when it when that happens
I don't know it
Can I ask you sir? I did this one time and they pulled out like the death card, you know
and um
My friend died basically three months after that
Did that have anything to do with that card reading or was that completely unrelated because I'm telling you
That was my best friend and then death because of that. No, and
I almost kind of was like all the cards told the story
Yeah, you know
If you didn't do drugs that night like he would have been fine
So I kind of don't understand it
Well, maybe because maybe it wasn't actual, you know, it's just like a little warning of like a prepare yourself
There might be something like that, but you know, you know always have you know, it can be a death of a person or it can be
an ending of some
Can we only say a prayer for him even if you're right?
Yeah, sure
Can I say a prayer for my friend? Yes, go ahead
Okay, the name of the Father Son and the Holy Spirit, if you're Muslim or Islam or whatever you are, it doesn't matter
The name of the Father Son and the Holy Spirit, my friend Adrian, I hope that you're not in hell
I hope that you're not suffering and predatory. I want to see you in heaven one day when I come back with you
God bless you. It's not where you're going. Hold on. It goes. Go on. I'm in the middle of a prayer. You fuck not
What are you doing, dude? I
Love you. God bless you. God take care of you. Holy Mother Mary, please
Pray for my friend in the name of the Father Son, Holy Spirit, Amen
Hey
Don't disrespect not unlike that ghost like you are don't do that
Yeah, I heard really clear
Very clear. You're making a mockery of it. I don't appreciate that. I
Was a mockery of my friend. What are you talking about?
I
Didn't make a mockery of my friend, are you fucking out of your mind?
Everybody gave you the respect soon as ghost came on he says something
I apologize. Yeah, thank you. Thank you. That's okay. We can move on. We can move on
I didn't mean this to me in the
next 15 minutes. I just wanted
you know, pay respects to my
friend man. Okay. Let's move
forward. I already apologized.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Your
friend. You know what? Before
I go to bed, you know, when I
pray, I'll keep him in my
prayers. Adrian, this is named
AJ he's in my purse. I apologize
His drug name is Jason I want to say AJ, but should I say I'm gonna say AJ and then I don't give my first
Which name you use it's the same person. Okay, but I'm apologizing. I didn't mean to suspect at all
I I forget I've already forgiven you 17 times. So I have to say fuck off
You're too focused. You can even understand. Oh my god. I mean, okay
How's your night going site? How you doing?
It was pretty good because like, you know, my friend came over and like is
And she wanted to help me clean and then
And they also
Did they have uh, yeah, he had a DMT. I got a hold on one second. What's that again?
You guys talk for a second. So it gets on brother
Luigi you're a faggot nigga. I don't like you you're fat you're ugly your wife is a bitch